flyaero.com 2017-12-19

# Aerocontractors the reliable way to fly - Book cheap flights flyaero.com

This website is brought to you by Aero Contractors Company of Nigeria Limited (Aero).  Aero respects your privacy and is committed to protect the personal information that you share with us.

****Information Collection**  
**Personal information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, email address, a home, postal or other physical address, other contact information, title, birth date, gender, other information when needed to provide a service you requested.  
When you browse our website, you do so anonymously, unless you have previously indicated that you wish Aero to remember your login and password. We don’t automatically collect personal information, including your email address. We do log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer) to give us an idea of which part of our website you visit and how long you spend there. But we do not link your IP address to any personal information unless you have logged in to our website.  
Aero collects personal information when you make a reservation, participate in an online survey, when you ask to be included in an email or other mailing list, or when you submit your personal information to Aero for any other reason. From time to time, Aero receives personal information from business partners and vendors. Aero only uses such information if it has been collected in accordance with acceptable privacy practices consistent with this Policy and applicable laws.

**How** **we may use your personal data** **  
** When personal information is collected, we will inform you at the point of collection the purpose for the collection (e.g. reservation, Marketing purposes, special promotions, etc.). Generally, the purposes include:

  * To help us identify you
  * Administration
  * Statistical analysis
  * Customer profiling and analyzing your purchasing preference
  * Fraud prevention and detection
  * Billing and other fulfillment
  * To notify you of any changes to this website or our services which may affect you
  * Security vetting
  * Improving our services

Aero will not transfer your personal information to third parties without your consent, except under the limited conditions described under the discussion entitled “Information Sharing and Disclosure” below.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure** **  
** Your personal information is never shared outside Aero without your permission, except under conditions explained below. Inside Aero, data is stored in controlled servers with limited access.

Aero may send your personal information to other companies or people under any of the following circumstances: when we have your consent to share the information; we need to share your information to provide the service or booking you have requested; we need to send the information to companies who work on behalf of Aero to provide the requested service to you (we will only provide those companies the information they need to deliver the service, and they are prohibited from using that information for any other purpose). We will also disclose your personal information if required to do so by law, to enforce our Terms and Conditions, or in urgent circumstances, to protect personal safety, the public or our websites.

**Data Security** **  
** In certain areas of our websites, Aero uses industry-standard SSL-encryption to enhance the security of data transmissions (Powered by HITIT). While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure the security of the information you transmit to us, and so we urge you to take every precaution to protect your personal data when you are on the Internet. Change your passwords often, use a combination of letters and numbers, and make sure you use a secure browser.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy** **  
** Aero will amend this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will make that information available by posting a notice on this site. We advise you check this policy occasionally to ensure you are aware of the most recent version which will apply each time you access this website.

**Questions or Suggestions** **  
** If you have questions or concerns about our collection, use, or disclosure of your personal information, please email us at aero@acn.aero or write to us at Aero Contractors Company of Nigeria Limited, (Private Terminal), Murtala Muhammed Airport, Ikeja, Lagos State, Nigeria.
